{
    "subject": "Shuji_Kataoka",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "S&M_Hunter",
    "human_readable": "Shuji Kataoka directed the film S&M Hunter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.890906035900116,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Shuji Kataoka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8020005226135254,
            "question": "Who directed the film S&M Hunter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.801993727684021,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Shuji Kataoka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7777149081230164,
            "question": "Is Shuji Kataoka a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5263703465461731,
            "question": "Who are some actors in the film S&M Hunter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4959460496902466,
            "question": "What is the plot of S&M Hunter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4049763083457947,
            "question": "What genre might the film S&M Hunter belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38596072793006897,
            "question": "Where was S&M Hunter filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32874804735183716,
            "question": "What year was S&M Hunter released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19659383594989777,
            "question": "Has S&M Hunter received any critical acclaim?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Shuji Kataoka directed the film S&M Hunter.",
            "html": "yago_17321_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was S&M Hunter released?",
            "html": "yago_17321_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was S&M Hunter filmed?",
            "html": "yago_17321_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the film S&M Hunter belong to?",
            "html": "yago_17321_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17321_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can determine that the triple is supported by the documents. \n\nThe key \"output\" will have a value of \"yes\".\n\nHere's why:\n\n* The document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17321/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt mentions Shuji Kataoka as the director of the film \"S&M Hunter\".\n* Another document, file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17321/re-ranker-msmarco/70.txt, confirms that Shuji Kataoka directed many action pink films including \"S&M HUNTER\".\n\nSo, the information in the documents supports the triple: Shuji Kataoka directed the film S&M Hunter.\n\nHere's the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Shuji Kataoka directed the film \"S&M Hunter.\" Specifically, the document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17321/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt states: \"Certainly, the concept of a film about a chauvinist superhero that tames his female adversaries with his expert rope work is too bizarre to easily forget, and promises to thoroughly undercut the noble and self-righteous image projected by traditional western heroes. Such is the endurance of the character that Kataoka, also known for his Subway Serial Rape series, used him in a cluster of films between 1985 and 1987, of which this particular title is the penultimate.\" Additionally, file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17321/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt also mentions that \"Directed by Shuji Kataoka\". Therefore, the query \"Shuji Kataoka directed the film S&M Hunter\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}